<class>Priest
    <tree id="0" name="Discipline">
        <talent index="1" name="Unbreakable Will" icon="MageArmor.png" prereq="-1">
            <rank index="1">Increases your chance to resist Stun, Fear, and Silence effects by an additional 3%.</rank>
            <rank index="2">Increases your chance to resist Stun, Fear, and Silence effects by an additional 6%.</rank>
            <rank index="3">Increases your chance to resist Stun, Fear, and Silence effects by an additional 9%.</rank>
            <rank index="4">Increases your chance to resist Stun, Fear, and Silence effects by an additional 12%.</rank>
            <rank index="5">Increases your chance to resist Stun, Fear, and Silence effects by an additional 15%.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="2" name="Mental Dexterity" icon="MindMastery.png" prereq="-1">
            <rank index="1">Reduces the Mana cost of your instant cast spells by 3%.</rank>
            <rank index="2">Reduces the Mana cost of your instant cast spells by 6%.</rank>
            <rank index="3">Reduces the Mana cost of your instant cast spells by 9%.</rank>
            <rank index="4">Reduces the Mana cost of your instant cast spells by 12%.</rank>
            <rank index="5">Reduces the Mana cost of your instant cast spells by 15%.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="4" name="Martyrdom" icon="Tranquility.png" prereq="-1">
            <rank index="1">Gives you a 50% chance to gain the Focused Casting effect that lasts for 6 sec after being the victim of a melee or ranged critical strike.  The Focused Casting effect prevents you from losing casting time when taking damage.</rank>
            <rank index="2">Gives you a 100% chance to gain the Focused Casting effect that lasts for 6 sec after being the victim of a melee or ranged critical strike.  The Focused Casting effect prevents you from losing casting time when taking damage.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="5" name="Meditation" icon="Sleep.png" prereq="-1">
            <rank index="1">Allows 10% of your Mana regeneration to continue while casting.</rank>
            <rank index="2">Allows 20% of your Mana regeneration to continue while casting.</rank>
            <rank index="3">Allows 30% of your Mana regeneration to continue while casting.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="6" name="Improved Power Word: Fortitude" icon="WordFortitude.png" prereq="-1">
            <rank index="1">Increases the effect of your Power Word: Fortitude and Prayer of Fortitude spells by 15%.</rank>
            <rank index="2">Increases the effect of your Power Word: Fortitude and Prayer of Fortitude spells by 30%.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="8" name="Silent Resolve" icon="ManaRegenTotem.png" prereq="-1">
            <rank index="1">Reduces the threat generated by your spells by 5% and the chance your helpful spells will be dispelled by 8%.</rank>
            <rank index="2">Reduces the threat generated by your spells by 10% and the chance your helpful spells will be dispelled by 16%.</rank>
            <rank index="3">Reduces the threat generated by your spells by 15% and the chance your helpful spells will be dispelled by 24%.</rank>
            <rank index="4">Reduces the threat generated by your spells by 20% and the chance your helpful spells will be dispelled by 32%.</rank>
            <rank index="5">Reduces the threat generated by your spells by 25% and the chance your helpful spells will be dispelled by 40%.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="9" name="Inner Focus" icon="WindWalkOn.png" prereq="-1">
            <rank index="1">When activated, reduces the Mana cost of your next spell by 100% and increases its critical effect chance by 25% if it is capable of a critical effect.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="10" name="Body and Soul" icon="Invisibilty.png" prereq="6">
            <rank index="1">Increases your Spirit and Stamina by 2%.</rank>
            <rank index="2">Increases your Spirit and Stamina by 4%.</rank>
            <rank index="3">Increases your Spirit and Stamina by 6%.</rank>
            <rank index="4">Increases your Spirit and Stamina by 8%.</rank>
            <rank index="5">Increases your Spirit and Stamina by 10%.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="12" name="Improved Power Word: Shield" icon="PowerWordShield.png" prereq="-1">
            <rank index="1">Increases the damage absorbed by your Power Word: Shield by 5%.</rank>
            <rank index="2">Increases the damage absorbed by your Power Word: Shield by 10%.</rank>
            <rank index="3">Increases the damage absorbed by your Power Word: Shield by 15%.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="16" name="Improved Inner Fire" icon="InnerFire.png" prereq="-1">
            <rank index="1">Your Inner Fire spell reduces critical damage taken from Physical attacks by 10%.</rank>
            <rank index="2">Your Inner Fire spell reduces critical damage taken from Physical attacks by 20%.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="17" name="Force of Will" icon="SlowingTotem.png" prereq="-1">
            <rank index="1">Increases your spell damage and critical strike chance by 1%.</rank>
            <rank index="2">Increases your spell damage and critical strike chance by 2%.</rank>
            <rank index="3">Increases your spell damage and critical strike chance by 3%.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="18" name="Divine Spirit" icon="DivineSpirit.png" prereq="6">
            <rank index="1">Holy power infuses the target, increasing their Spirit by 17 for 30 min.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="22" name="Mental Agility" icon="Hibernation.png" prereq="-1">
            <rank index="1">Gives your instant cast spells a 20% chance to reduce the cast time of your next spell by 0.1 sec.</rank>
            <rank index="2">Gives your instant cast spells a 40% chance to reduce the cast time of your next spell by 0.2 sec.</rank>
            <rank index="3">Gives your instant cast spells a 60% chance to reduce the cast time of your next spell by 0.3 sec.</rank>
            <rank index="4">Gives your instant cast spells a 80% chance to reduce the cast time of your next spell by 0.4 sec.</rank>
            <rank index="5">Gives your instant cast spells a 100% chance to reduce the cast time of your next spell by 0.5 sec.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="25" name="Power Infusion" icon="PowerInfusion.png" prereq="17">
            <rank index="1">Infuses the target with power, increasing their spell damage and healing by 20%.  Lasts 15 sec.</rank>
        </talent>
        <arrow index="6" origin="6" type="-1" cap="0"></arrow>
        <arrow index="14" origin="10" type="0" cap="0"></arrow>
        <arrow index="21" origin="13" type="0" cap="0"></arrow>
    </tree>
    <tree id="1" name="Holy">
        <talent index="0" name="Spell Warding" icon="SpellWarding.png" prereq="-1">
            <rank index="1">Reduces all spell damage taken by 5%.</rank>
            <rank index="2">Reduces all spell damage taken by 10%.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="1" name="Searing Light" icon="SearingLightPriest.png" prereq="-1">
            <rank index="1">Gives your Smite and Holy Nova spells a 2% chance, and your Holy Fire spell a 4% chance, to disorient enemies for 2 sec.</rank>
            <rank index="2">Gives your Smite and Holy Nova spells a 4% chance, and your Holy Fire spell a 8% chance, to disorient enemies for 2 sec.</rank>
            <rank index="3">Gives your Smite and Holy Nova spells a 6% chance, and your Holy Fire spell a 12% chance, to disorient enemies for 2 sec.</rank>
            <rank index="4">Gives your Smite and Holy Nova spells a 8% chance, and your Holy Fire spell a 16% chance, to disorient enemies for 2 sec.</rank>
            <rank index="5">Gives your Smite and Holy Nova spells a 10% chance, and your Holy Fire spell a 20% chance, to disorient enemies for 2 sec.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="2" name="Inspiration" icon="LayOnHands.png" prereq="-1">
            <rank index="1">Increases your target's armor by 8% for 15 sec after getting a critical effect from your healing spells or effects.</rank>
            <rank index="2">Increases your target's armor by 16% for 15 sec after getting a critical effect from your healing spells or effects.</rank>
            <rank index="3">Increases your target's armor by 25% for 15 sec after getting a critical effect from your healing spells or effects.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="6" name="Holy Specialization" icon="Aspiration.png" prereq="-1">
            <rank index="1">Increases the critical effect chance of your Holy spells by 1%.</rank>
            <rank index="2">Increases the critical effect chance of your Holy spells by 2%.</rank>
            <rank index="3">Increases the critical effect chance of your Holy spells by 3%.</rank>
            <rank index="4">Increases the critical effect chance of your Holy spells by 4%.</rank>
            <rank index="5">Increases the critical effect chance of your Holy spells by 5%.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="7" name="Blessed Recovery" icon="BlessedRecovery.png" prereq="-1">
            <rank index="1">After being struck by a melee or ranged critical hit, heal 10% of the damage taken over 4 sec.  In addition, increases the amount healed by your Renew spell by 5%.</rank>
            <rank index="2">After being struck by a melee or ranged critical hit, heal 20% of the damage taken over 4 sec.  In addition, increases the amount healed by your Renew spell by 10%.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="8" name="Holy Nova" icon="HolyNova.png" prereq="-1">
            <rank index="1">Causes an explosion of holy light around the caster, causing 29 to 34 Holy damage to all enemy targets within 10 yards and healing all party members within 10 yards for 54 to 63.  These effects cause no threat.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="10" name="Healing Focus" icon="HealingFocus.png" prereq="-1">
            <rank index="1">Gives you a 20% chance to avoid interruption caused by damage, and reduces damage taken by 2%, while casting any healing spell.</rank>
            <rank index="2">Gives you a 40% chance to avoid interruption caused by damage, and reduces damage taken by 4%, while casting any healing spell.</rank>
            <rank index="3">Gives you a 60% chance to avoid interruption caused by damage, and reduces damage taken by 6%, while casting any healing spell.</rank>
            <rank index="4">Gives you a 80% chance to avoid interruption caused by damage, and reduces damage taken by 8%, while casting any healing spell.</rank>
            <rank index="5">Gives you a 100% chance to avoid interruption caused by damage, and reduces damage taken by 10%, while casting any healing spell.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="11" name="Holy Reach" icon="Purify.png" prereq="-1">
            <rank index="1">Increases the range of your Smite and Holy Fire spells and the radius of your Prayer of Healing and Holy Nova spells by 10%.</rank>
            <rank index="2">Increases the range of your Smite and Holy Fire spells and the radius of your Prayer of Healing and Holy Nova spells by 20%.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="13" name="Divine Fury" icon="SealOfWrath.png" prereq="1">
            <rank index="1">Reduces the casting time of your Smite, Holy Fire and Greater Heal spells by 0.1 sec.</rank>
            <rank index="2">Reduces the casting time of your Smite, Holy Fire and Greater Heal spells by 0.2 sec.</rank>
            <rank index="3">Reduces the casting time of your Smite, Holy Fire and Greater Heal spells by 0.3 sec.</rank>
            <rank index="4">Reduces the casting time of your Smite, Holy Fire and Greater Heal spells by 0.4 sec.</rank>
            <rank index="5">Reduces the casting time of your Smite, Holy Fire and Greater Heal spells by 0.5 sec.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="14" name="Divinity" icon="SealOfSalvation.png" prereq="10">
            <rank index="1">Reduces the casting time of your Smite, Holy Fire, Prayer of Healing and Heal spells by 0.1 sec.</rank>
            <rank index="2">Reduces the casting time of your Smite, Holy Fire, Prayer of Healing and Heal spells by 0.2 sec.</rank>
            <rank index="3">Reduces the casting time of your Smite, Holy Fire, Prayer of Healing and Heal spells by 0.3 sec.</rank>
            <rank index="4">Reduces the casting time of your Smite, Holy Fire, Prayer of Healing and Heal spells by 0.4 sec.</rank>
            <rank index="5">Reduces the casting time of your Smite, Holy Fire, Prayer of Healing and Heal spells by 0.5 sec.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="16" name="Improved Healing" icon="Heal.png" prereq="-1">
            <rank index="1">Increases the amount healed by your healing spells by 5%.</rank>
            <rank index="2">Increases the amount healed by your healing spells by 10%.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="17" name="Desperate Prayer" icon="DesperatePrayer.png" prereq="-1">
            <rank index="1">Instantly heals the caster for 546 to 654.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="18" name="Spiritual Healing" icon="MoonGlow.png" prereq="-1">
            <rank index="1">Reduces the Mana cost of your Holy Nova, Desperate Prayer, Prayer of Healing, Heal, and Greater Heal spells by 5%.</rank>
            <rank index="2">Reduces the Mana cost of your Holy Nova, Desperate Prayer, Prayer of Healing, Heal, and Greater Heal spells by 10%.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="22" name="Spiritual Guidance" icon="SpiritualGuidance.png" prereq="-1">
            <rank index="1">Increases spell damage and healing by up to 5% of your total Spirit.</rank>
            <rank index="2">Increases spell damage and healing by up to 10% of your total Spirit.</rank>
            <rank index="3">Increases spell damage and healing by up to 15% of your total Spirit.</rank>
            <rank index="4">Increases spell damage and healing by up to 20% of your total Spirit.</rank>
            <rank index="5">Increases spell damage and healing by up to 25% of your total Spirit.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="25" name="Icon of Redemption" icon="HolyProtection.png" prereq="17">
            <rank index="1">Summons an Icon of Redemption with 600 health in front of the caster.  Prevents a party member within 20 yds of the Icon of Redemption from dying, healing for 872 to 1033, when they take lethal damage.  Lasts 1 minute.</rank>
        </talent>
        <arrow index="5" origin="1" type="0" cap="-1"></arrow>
        <arrow index="9" origin="1" type="0" cap="0"></arrow>
        <arrow index="10" origin="10" type="-1" cap="0"></arrow>
        <arrow index="21" origin="17" type="0" cap="0"></arrow>
    </tree>
    <tree id="2" name="Shadow">
        <talent index="1" name="Shadow Affinity" icon="ShadowWard.png" prereq="-1">
            <rank index="1">Reduces the threat generated by your Shadow spells by 5% and increases the effect of your Fade ability by 5%.</rank>
            <rank index="2">Reduces the threat generated by your Shadow spells by 10% and increases the effect of your Fade ability by 10%.</rank>
            <rank index="3">Reduces the threat generated by your Shadow spells by 15% and increases the effect of your Fade ability by 15%.</rank>
            <rank index="4">Reduces the threat generated by your Shadow spells by 20% and increases the effect of your Fade ability by 20%.</rank>
            <rank index="5">Reduces the threat generated by your Shadow spells by 25% and increases the effect of your Fade ability by 25%.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="2" name="Blackout" icon="GatherShadows.png" prereq="-1">
            <rank index="1">Gives your Shadow damage spells a 2% chance to stun the target for 3 sec.</rank>
            <rank index="2">Gives your Shadow damage spells a 4% chance to stun the target for 3 sec.</rank>
            <rank index="3">Gives your Shadow damage spells a 6% chance to stun the target for 3 sec.</rank>
            <rank index="4">Gives your Shadow damage spells a 8% chance to stun the target for 3 sec.</rank>
            <rank index="5">Gives your Shadow damage spells a 10% chance to stun the target for 3 sec.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="4" name="Improved Psychic Scream" icon="PsychicScream.png" prereq="-1">
            <rank index="1">Reduces the cooldown of your Psychic Scream spell by 2 sec.</rank>
            <rank index="2">Reduces the cooldown of your Psychic Scream spell by 4 sec.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="5" name="Shadow Focus" icon="BurningSpirit.png" prereq="-1">
            <rank index="1">Reduces your target's chance to resist your Shadow spells by 2%.</rank>
            <rank index="2">Reduces your target's chance to resist your Shadow spells by 4%.</rank>
            <rank index="3">Reduces your target's chance to resist your Shadow spells by 6%.</rank>
            <rank index="4">Reduces your target's chance to resist your Shadow spells by 8%.</rank>
            <rank index="5">Reduces your target's chance to resist your Shadow spells by 10%.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="6" name="Improved Shadow Word: Pain" icon="ShadowWordPain.png" prereq="-1">
            <rank index="1">Increases the duration of your Shadow Word: Pain spell by 3 sec.</rank>
            <rank index="2">Increases the duration of your Shadow Word: Pain spell by 6 sec.</rank>
            <rank index="3">Increases the duration of your Shadow Word: Pain spell by 9 sec.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="8" name="Improved Mind Blast" icon="UnholyFrenzy.png" prereq="-1">
            <rank index="1">Reduces the cooldown of your Mind Blast spell by 0.5 sec.</rank>
            <rank index="2">Reduces the cooldown of your Mind Blast spell by 1 sec.</rank>
            <rank index="3">Reduces the cooldown of your Mind Blast spell by 1.5 sec.</rank>
            <rank index="4">Reduces the cooldown of your Mind Blast spell by 2 sec.</rank>
            <rank index="5">Reduces the cooldown of your Mind Blast spell by 2.5 sec.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="9" name="Shadow Reach" icon="ChillTouch.png" prereq="-1">
            <rank index="1">Increases the range of your Shadow damage spells by 6%.</rank>
            <rank index="2">Increases the range of your Shadow damage spells by 13%.</rank>
            <rank index="3">Increases the range of your Shadow damage spells by 20%.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="10" name="Mind Flay" icon="SiphonMana.png" prereq="-1">
            <rank index="1">Assault the target's mind with Shadow energy, causing 75 Shadow damage over 3 sec and slowing their movement speed by 50%.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="13" name="Spirit Tap" icon="Requiem.png" prereq="-1">
            <rank index="1">Gives you a 2% chance, when your Shadow spells deal damage, to gain a 100% bonus to your Spirit.  For the duration, your Mana will regenerate at a 50% rate while casting.  Lasts 15 sec.</rank>
            <rank index="2">Gives you a 4% chance, when your Shadow spells deal damage, to gain a 100% bonus to your Spirit.  For the duration, your Mana will regenerate at a 50% rate while casting.  Lasts 15 sec.</rank>
            <rank index="3">Gives you a 6% chance, when your Shadow spells deal damage, to gain a 100% bonus to your Spirit.  For the duration, your Mana will regenerate at a 50% rate while casting.  Lasts 15 sec.</rank>
            <rank index="4">Gives you a 8% chance, when your Shadow spells deal damage, to gain a 100% bonus to your Spirit.  For the duration, your Mana will regenerate at a 50% rate while casting.  Lasts 15 sec.</rank>
            <rank index="5">Gives you a 10% chance, when your Shadow spells deal damage, to gain a 100% bonus to your Spirit.  For the duration, your Mana will regenerate at a 50% rate while casting.  Lasts 15 sec.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="14" name="Dark Accord" icon="ConsumeMagic.png" prereq="-1">
            <rank index="1">Gives your Mind Flay and Mind Blast spells a 25% chance reduce the Mana cost of your next Shadow spell by 20% but requiring you to sacrifice Health equal to 50% of the base cost of the spell.</rank>
            <rank index="2">Gives your Mind Flay and Mind Blast spells a 25% chance reduce the Mana cost of your next Shadow spell by 40% but requiring you to sacrifice Health equal to 50% of the base cost of the spell.</rank>
            <rank index="3">Gives your Mind Flay and Mind Blast spells a 25% chance reduce the Mana cost of your next Shadow spell by 60% but requiring you to sacrifice Health equal to 50% of the base cost of the spell.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="16" name="Silence" icon="ImpPhaseShift.png" prereq="8">
            <rank index="1">Silences the target, preventing them from casting spells for 5 sec.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="17" name="Vampiric Embrace" icon="UnsummonBuilding.png" prereq="-1">
            <rank index="1">Afflicts your target with Shadow energy that causes all party members to be healed for 10% of any Shadow spell damage you deal for 1 min.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="18" name="Improved Vampiric Embrace" icon="ImprovedVampiricEmbrace.png" prereq="17">
            <rank index="1">Increases the percentage healed by Vampiric Embrace by an additional 10%.</rank>
            <rank index="2">Increases the percentage healed by Vampiric Embrace by an additional 20%.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="19" name="Shadow Weaving" icon="BlackPlague.png" prereq="-1">
            <rank index="1">Your Shadow damage spells have a 20% chance to cause your target to be vulnerable to Shadow damage.  This vulnerability increases the Shadow damage dealt to your target by 3% and lasts 15 sec.  Stacks up to 5 times.</rank>
            <rank index="2">Your Shadow damage spells have a 40% chance to cause your target to be vulnerable to Shadow damage.  This vulnerability increases the Shadow damage dealt to your target by 3% and lasts 15 sec.  Stacks up to 5 times.</rank>
            <rank index="3">Your Shadow damage spells have a 60% chance to cause your target to be vulnerable to Shadow damage.  This vulnerability increases the Shadow damage dealt to your target by 3% and lasts 15 sec.  Stacks up to 5 times.</rank>
            <rank index="4">Your Shadow damage spells have a 80% chance to cause your target to be vulnerable to Shadow damage.  This vulnerability increases the Shadow damage dealt to your target by 3% and lasts 15 sec.  Stacks up to 5 times.</rank>
            <rank index="5">Your Shadow damage spells have a 100% chance to cause your target to be vulnerable to Shadow damage.  This vulnerability increases the Shadow damage dealt to your target by 3% and lasts 15 sec.  Stacks up to 5 times.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="22" name="Darkness" icon="Twilight (2).png" prereq="-1">
            <rank index="1">Increases your Shadow spell damage by 2%.</rank>
            <rank index="2">Increases your Shadow spell damage by 4%.</rank>
            <rank index="3">Increases your Shadow spell damage by 6%.</rank>
            <rank index="4">Increases your Shadow spell damage by 8%.</rank>
            <rank index="5">Increases your Shadow spell damage by 10%.</rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="25" name="Shadowform" icon="Shadowform.png" prereq="17">
            <rank index="1">Assume a Shadowform, increasing your Shadow damage by 15% and reducing Physical damage done to you by 15%.  However, you may not cast Holy spells while in this form.</rank>
        </talent>
        <arrow index="12" origin="8" type="0" cap="0"></arrow>
        <arrow index="17" origin="17" type="-1" cap="2"></arrow>
        <arrow index="21" origin="17" type="0" cap="0"></arrow>
    </tree>
</class>